{
    "subject": "resource/UD_Melilla",
    "predicate": "property/name",
    "object": "resource/Ricardo_Segura_Mart\u00ednez",
    "human_readable": "Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez is the name of UD Melilla.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9621986746788025,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez's role at UD Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8702369928359985,
            "question": "Who is Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8658159971237183,
            "question": "What is the name of UD Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7564322352409363,
            "question": "What does UD stand for in the name UD Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6023617386817932,
            "question": "Where is UD Melilla located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5969980955123901,
            "question": "What type of organization is UD Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.56490558385849,
            "question": "Is Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez a well-known figure in the world of sports?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5445153713226318,
            "question": "Is Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez associated with a sports team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5392014980316162,
            "question": "Are there any notable achievements associated with UD Melilla?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40867704153060913,
            "question": "What sport does UD Melilla play?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez is the name of UD Melilla.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4803_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any notable achievements associated with UD Melilla?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4803_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez associated with a sports team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4803_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez a well-known figure in the world of sports?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4803_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4803_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text states that Ud Melilla, also known as Uni\u00f3n Deportiva Melilla,  is a Spanish football club. It does not mention Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context information, the query \"Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez is the name of UD Melilla\" can be evaluated as follows:\n\n* The documents mention \"Ud Melilla\", but there is no mention of Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez being associated with the team.\n* The documents do mention Mohamed Mohamed, Juan Jose Calva\u00f1o, and Juan Hernandez as notable players who have played for Ud Melilla.\n\nTherefore, the answer to the query is:\n\n{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided context does not contain any information related to Ud Melilla's name or members, and instead provides details about their history, achievements in local championships, fan base, and league participation. There is no mention of a specific individual named Ricardo Segura Mart\u00ednez being the name of UD Melilla."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}